<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources xmlns:ns1="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <string-array name="step1_first_questions">
        
        <item>Do you experience (--)\’s existence and yours as two different existences?</item>
        
        <item>Are you suggesting that you perceive and experience (--) to have the same existence as yours?</item>
        
        <item>Are you absolutely certain you and (--) share the same existence?</item></string-array>
    <string-array name="step1_options">
        <item>1. Is (--) one entity?</item>
        <item>2. Is (--) able to self-produce?</item>
        <item>3. Do you need your mind\'s labels to exist as different entities?</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="step1_third_questions">
        
        <item>Can you see that (--) is not one entity, but made of parts?</item>
        
        <item>Do you see the red squares indicating the parts?</item>
        
        <item>The analysis found that (--) is not a singular entity but made of parts that you seem unable to see. Can you at least see that (--) is made up of a right and left side? </item>
        
        <item>The analysis found that (--) is not a singular entity but made of parts and halves. What is made of parts and halves is not singular and thus cannot be treated as a singular entity. (--) is not one entity.</item>
        
        <item>If (--) is not a singular entity, is it logical to treat (--) as a singular entity?</item>
        
        <item>The fact that (--) is not a singular entity but made of many parts and halves cannot co-exist with your belief that (--) is a singular entity. Do you agree that a singular entity should be singular?</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="step2_questions">
        
        <item>Did (--) generate her/his being?</item>
        
        <item>Did (--) self-produce without any parents?</item>
        
        <item>Did (--) self-generate without any artificial laboratory procedure, or other processes?</item>
        
        <item> This is incorrect. (--) did not self-generate because (--) lacks an individual nature of any kind that could do that.
            All living beings exist without any personal nature, thus no one can self-generate; instead, everyone is a manifestation of the same universal nature.

\n Thus, (--) is not different from you or anybody, and vice versa, as everyone is a product of the same universal nature and not their own.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="step3_questions">
        
        <item>Can this person exist as (--) without your mind\’s label of \“(--)\”? </item>
        
        <item>Do Humans invent and give labels to everything?</item>
        
        <item>If your mind did not name your body and mind as \“(==)\”, would people call you (==)? </item>
        
        <item>If you did not name this person \"(--)\", would they exist to you as (--)?</item>
        
        <item>If this person was already (--), would it make sense to label what is already (--) as \"(--)\" again?</item>
        
        <item>This person has been existing without any label until the label \"(--)\" was created and projected by your mind for convenience\'s sake.
            This way, everybody can function in concepts as \"(--)\" and \“you\” .</item>
        <item>Incorrect. Please consider reviewing</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="summary_finals">
        
        <item>
            Correct and Congratulations!
 \n\n By navigating the fundamental aspects of existence, you’ve grasped that (--) and you share the same origin and essence, devoid of any individual nature.
            \n Any distinctions between you two are relative and exist in mere labels only.
            \n Understanding the sameness we all share eliminates the basis for conflicts and unhappiness.
            \n Recognizing this reality is pivotal, as any conflict between you two or anyone else is fundamentally a conflict against oneself.
            \n
            A true peace and happiness await those who comprehend and practice this profound understanding.</item>
        
        <item>
           Now, empowered with the understanding and evidence that human senses have deceived humanity for centuries, you recognize the contradiction in the prevailing viewpoint that everyone possesses their own existence.
             \n This ignorance fuels conflicts, unhappiness, and suffering.
             \n Embracing this correct knowledge paves the simplest path to inexhaustible wisdom, peace, and happiness for you and the world.
 \n
             \n If you believe this app has the potential to break the endless cycle of self-made conflict, please help us spread the word.
 \n\n
            Thank you!
            Congratulations! You have completed all 3 Steps and Conclusions!
        </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="summary_questions">
        <item> 99 percent of humans are not aware that all people exist without individual existence.
            \n Then our minds invent labels such as \"(--)\", \"(==)\", \"you\", \"I\", \"they\", \”American\”, \”European\”, \”Asian\”, \”African\”, or \”Whatever\”.
\n The mind projects them onto people and wrongly believes them as facts about everyone.
            \n Our belief in various labels changes the truth about people and causes them to appear to have a different existence from ours, even though everyone lacks individual existence.

\n\n
            All differences between people are relative and exist in concepts only as you discovered in Step #3.
        </item>
        
        <item>
(--) and you exist without independent existence as neither one of you is a singular entity, and neither possesses an individual nature capable of self-production;
            instead, you both share the common origin and essence of the same universal nature, comprising both physical and non-physical elements, rather than originating autonomously.
            \n\n
            Considering this, does it make logical sense to treat (--) and you as two distinct existences?

        </item>
        
        <item>
            Singular entities capable of self-production, a characteristic needed for possessing one’s own existence, do not exist, as you learned from completing Step #1 and Step #2.
            \n\n
            Recognizing that (--) and you lack individual existence, it becomes illogical to perceive and treat you and (--) as two distinct entities.
        </item>
        
        <item>
            Correct. You and (--) lack individual existence as you’re not singular entities with the capacity for self-production.  Instead, both of you are compositions of the same universal nature, comprising of countless physical and non-physical elements, rather than originating autonomously.
Your origin and essence are identical, and any perceived distinctions do not belong to any individual; they are relative and arise from your mind\'s conceptualizations. Recognizing this, any action against (--) is essentially an action against yourself, and vice versa.
            \n\n
    Do you now recognize that any conflict between you two, or anyone else, is essentially a conflict against oneself?
        </item>
        
        <item>
           Take a moment to reflect profoundly on each question. Envision the presented information without the influence of preconceived notions to grasp life’s facts and the truth of this conclusion.
        </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="summary_texts">
        
        <item>In the beginning, you said that you perceive and experience (--)\’s existence and yours as two different existences.</item>
        
        <item> To claim a true individual existence (--) and you need to be two different existences where each of you is:
            \n\n
            \n1. One entity.
            \n2. Able to self-generate.
            \n3. Existing as (--) and you without your mind\'s labels.
            \n\n
        However, you successfully completed all 3 Steps and found the opposite to be true about (--) and you.
        </item>
        
        <item>You discovered that (--) and you are:
            \n1. Not one entity.
            \n2. Not able to generate yourselves.
            \n3. In need of your mind\’s labels of “\(--)\” and \“you\” to exist as (--) and you.
            \n
             \n\n  This proves that (--) and you are not two different existences, and your senses are not showing this fact correctly.
        </item>
        
        <item> Conclusion: it appears to your mind that (--) and you possess different existences, but when examined, (--) and you do not.
            \n This proves that your senses are lying to you because (--) and you appear to possess individual existence, but that is not true.</item>
        
        <item> Both you and (--), along with everything else in the world, lack individual existence.
    \n Consequently, considering (--) and you as two distinct entities is illogical, as neither one of you is one entity and both of you lack individual nature that could independently bring about your existence.
    \n You both share the identical origin and essence of countless universal elements, encompassing both physical and nonphysical aspects.
    \n Any perceived distinctions are without different natures and thus are only relative, existing solely in conceptual labels such as \"(--)\", \"(==)\", \"you\", \"tall\", \"short\", etc. created by the mind, while our essence remains universally shared.</item>
        
        <item> Every living being manifests from the same universal nature, comprising both physical and non-physical elements, rather than originating autonomously.
\n Recognizing the identical universal essence and origin shared by everyone challenges the notion of multiple existences, revealing all-encompassing identical Universal existence.
\n
This insight dispels the misconception of different existences that we erroneously perceive and believe in.</item>
        
        <item>Since you and (--) share the same existence, why do humans believe in many different existences and experience them as real?</item>
    </string-array>
    <color name="black">#000000</color>
    <color name="black_transparent">#90000000</color>
    <color name="button_no">#60b600</color>
    <color name="button_no_focused">#6fd200</color>
    <color name="button_no_pressed">#509700</color>
    <color name="button_no_trans70">#7060b600</color>
    <color name="button_yes">#ff5252</color>
    <color name="button_yes_focused">#fd6565</color>
    <color name="button_yes_pressed">#fb2f2f</color>
    <color name="colorAccent">#60b600</color>
    <color name="colorPrimary">#60b600</color>
    <color name="colorPrimaryDark">#471321</color>
    <color name="light_gray">#F3F4F2</color>
    <color name="mainColor">#471321</color>
    <color name="textcolor">#D11903</color>
    <color name="trans_60_yellow">#60615401</color>
    <color name="white">#ffffff</color>
    <color name="white_trans">#90ffffff</color>
    <string name="add_photo" translatable="false">Add Photo to Start:</string>
    <string name="answerNo" translatable="false">No</string>
    <string name="answerYes" translatable="false">Yes</string>
    <string name="app_name" translatable="false">Peace Booster</string>
    <string name="arabic" translatable="false">عربى</string>
    <string name="ask_for_clarification">Ask for Clarification</string>
    <string name="buton_save" translatable="false">Save</string>
    <string name="button_agree" translatable="false">Agree</string>
    <string name="button_another_picture" translatable="false">Take Another Picture</string>
    <string name="button_disagree" translatable="false">Disagree</string>
    <string name="button_donate" translatable="false">DONATE</string>
    <string name="button_next" translatable="false">Next</string>
    <string name="button_ok" translatable="false">Ok</string>
    <string name="button_start_over" translatable="false">Start Over</string>
    <string name="button_start_over_or" translatable="false">or Start Over</string>
    <string name="button_text" translatable="false">Text</string>
    <string name="button_tweet" translatable="false">Tweet</string>
    <string name="cancel" translatable="false">Cancel</string>
    <string name="chinese">汉语</string>
    <string name="click_photo" translatable="false">Click on the photo to confirm if (--) is one entity.</string>
    <string name="close">close</string>
    <string name="com.google.firebase.crashlytics.mapping_file_id" ns1:ignore="UnusedResources,TypographyDashes" translatable="false">00000000000000000000000000000000</string>
    <string name="complete_step1" translatable="false">Correct! In Step 1 you’ve recognized that (--) is not one entity but a composite of various parts and halves.
       \n  By acknowledging this, you’ve taken the first step towards understanding the true nature of existence.
    \n    Remember, (--) is not one entity, and this realization sets the foundation for the next steps in discovering the profound sameness and interconnectedness we all share.
        \n\n
        Congratulations. You have completed Step #1.</string>
    <string name="complete_step2" translatable="false">  Congratulations! Step 2 has revealed that (--) did not self-produce because (--) lacks individual nature of any kind that could; instead (--) is a manifestation of the universal nature and its countless and ever-changing physical and non-physical elements.
\n Thus, (--) is not different from you or anybody, and vice versa, as everyone is a product of the same universal nature and not their own.
\n This understanding challenges the notion of individual existence and highlights the universal origin and essence we all share.
\n By grasping this fact, you’ve paved the way for deeper insights into the nature of existence most people remain unaware of.

        \n\n Congratulations. You have completed Step #2!</string>
    <string name="complete_step3" translatable="false"> Correct. In Step 3, you explored the facts of your mind\'s labeling and discovered that the person in the photo cannot exist as (--) without your mind\’s label of \"(--)\".
        \n This realization extends to your own existence, emphasizing the role of mental labels in shaping perceptions and experiences.
        \n Please remember, that the label \"(--)\" is merely a construct of your mind. All labels originate from your mind rather than from the side of any physical forms you are experiencing.
        \n Recognizing this challenges the notion of separate existences, as human distinctions exist only in labels.
        \n Reflect on how your experience may contradict this fundamental truth.
       \n\n Congratulations. You have completed Step #3.</string>
    <string name="correct_answer_">CorrectAnswer: %s</string>
    <string name="current_language" translatable="false">English</string>
    <string name="default_web_client_id" translatable="false">648181259163-mhekg84a79mbs3rfm6f5j1kvfvsucnu6.apps.googleusercontent.com</string>
    <string name="english" translatable="false">English</string>
    <string name="enter_photo_name" translatable="false">Name this Person.</string>
    <string name="enter_username" translatable="false">Enter your name.</string>
    <string name="exit" translatable="false">Exit</string>
    <string name="finish">Finish</string>
    <string name="from_gallery" translatable="false">From Your Gallery.</string>
    <string name="gcm_defaultSenderId" translatable="false">648181259163</string>
    <string name="go_to_conclusion" translatable="false">Go to Conclusion</string>
    <string name="go_to_point2" translatable="false">Go to Step #2</string>
    <string name="go_to_point3" translatable="false">Go to Step #3</string>
    <string name="google_api_key" translatable="false">AIzaSyA8XmJpCcWN_Pq9QV3qnMjaODaoYB23q6w</string>
    <string name="google_app_id" translatable="false">1:648181259163:android:2f2fe9609a4137846b5f3e</string>
    <string name="google_crash_reporting_api_key" translatable="false">AIzaSyA8XmJpCcWN_Pq9QV3qnMjaODaoYB23q6w</string>
    <string name="google_storage_bucket" translatable="false">peace-booster.appspot.com</string>
    <string name="hebrew" translatable="false">עִברִית</string>
    <string name="however" translatable="false">However,</string>
    <string name="link_step1" translatable="false"><b><u>Step #1</u></b></string>
    <string name="link_step1_or" translatable="false"><b><u>or Step #1</u></b></string>
    <string name="link_step2" translatable="false"><b><u>Step #2</u></b></string>
    <string name="link_step2_or" translatable="false"><b><u>or Step #2</u></b></string>
    <string name="link_step3" translatable="false"><b><u>Step #3</u></b></string>
    <string name="link_step3_again" translatable="false"><b><u> Step #3 again</u></b></string>
    <string name="narrative" translatable="false">
        WELCOME TO PEACE BOOSTER.
        \n\n
        Embark on a journey to discover the key to a life of effortless peace, fulfillment, and joy.
         \n
        Uncover the truth beyond your mind\’s deceptions, a truth that has the power to end injustice, war, and suffering worldwide.
         \n
        Unveil the true nature of the world and understand the role of your mind in shaping it.
    </string>
    <string name="note" translatable="false">NOTE</string>
    <string name="official_content">
The Foundation of this App.
\n\n
At first glance, the world appears teeming with diversity. However, undeniable facts about everybody challenge and contradict our everyday perception and experience of each other as different and separate.
\n
Each of us experiences ourselves as different and separate from everybody else, but is this a fact or an illusion?
Find out for yourself:
\n\n
To truly exist independently, a person must meet three criteria:
\n
1. Unity: The person must be a single, indivisible entity. If they are not one thing, they cannot be considered one person.
\n
2. Independence: The person must have an independent nature that brings about their own existence. If their existence depends on everything else, then they lack a unique essence that makes them different from others.
\n
3. Concept-Free Existence: The person must exist without relying on our mind\’s label of "a person." If they exist only as a concept, it means they are a person only in the ideas our mind creates, projects, and believes in.
\n\n
We invite you to use our app to explore how everyone truly exists and discover these insights for yourself. Have fun!

    </string>
    <string name="official_rules"><u>The Foundation of this App.</u></string>
    <string name="official_title">The Foundation of this App.</string>
    <string name="open">open</string>
    <string name="option_explain" translatable="false">Examine each of the three points below to discover if (--) and you are two different existences.</string>
    <string name="p4_disagree" translatable="false">Incorrect: Please consider reviewing Step #2, or Start Over.</string>
    <string name="p9_second_sentence" translatable="false">These are the incorruptible facts of how everyone exists with no exceptions. Do you see and understand this?</string>
    <string name="permission_denied" translatable="false">Permission Granted</string>
    <string name="photo_name" translatable="false">Name this Person</string>
    <string name="please_donate" translatable="false">Please donate to improve and keep this app free to all.</string>
    <string name="project_id" translatable="false">peace-booster</string>
    <string name="q3_dialog_alert" translatable="false"> Your senses are functioning correctly, indicating a deep understanding and uncorrupted senses.
Consider that all beings, including (--), are manifestations of the same universal physical and non-physical elements, without individual ability to generate themselves; thus, everyone is identical and shares a common origin.
        There are no differences between people, except for relative ones, like "\you\", \"me\", "\short\" or \"tall\" which arise through concepts invented and projected by our minds.
        This realization is the path to true peace and happiness.
        Since you and (--) are without individual existence, any action against (--) is an action against yourself and vice versa.
        You may not need this app but feel free to use for further understanding.
 </string>
    <string name="question_skipped">Question was skipped</string>
    <string name="read_articles">Read Articles</string>
    <string name="retake" translatable="false">Retake Photo</string>
    <string name="save" translatable="false">Save</string>
    <string name="share_app">Share App</string>
    <string name="share_congressman" translatable="false">Share it with your Congressman:</string>
    <string name="share_senators" translatable="false">Share it with your Senators:</string>
    <string name="start" translatable="false">Start</string>
    <string name="step1" translatable="false">1</string>
    <string name="step1_incorrect_alert" translatable="false">Really? In that case, something is not displaying correctly on your phone, but please keep going.</string>
    <string name="step1_incorrect_alert2" translatable="false">  We understand this is challenging. Please acknowledge what you see, not what you believe about people. An honest observation is the key to recognizing this fact.
</string>
    <string name="step1_incorrect_alert3" translatable="false">We understand this is challenging; however, your answer is incorrect.</string>
    <string name="step1_second_question" translatable="false"> To confirm that (--) and you are two different existences, each of you must be one self-generated entity and exist as different without your mind\’s labels of \"(--)\" and \“you\”.
\n These three qualities are necessary for (--) and you as a genuine claim of individual existence.</string>
    <string name="step1_third_question_title" translatable="false">Is (--) a singular entity?</string>
    <string name="step2" translatable="false">2</string>
    <string name="step2_incorrect_alert" translatable="false">We understand this may be challenging. Let’s try this differently..</string>
    <string name="step2_title" translatable="false">Is (--) able to self-produce?</string>
    <string name="step3" translatable="false">3</string>
    <string name="step3_incorrect_alert" translatable="false">We understand this may be challenging. Let’s try this differently.</string>
    <string name="step3_incorrect_alert2" translatable="false">We understand this may be challenging. Please repeat  Point #1.</string>
    <string name="step3_incorrect_alert3" translatable="false">We understand this may be challenging, but you are almost there. Please do not give up now; you will realize this truth very soon.</string>
    <string name="step3_title" translatable="false">Can (--) exist as \“(--)\” without your mind\’s label?</string>
    <string name="summary_title" translatable="false">What you have discovered: </string>
    <string name="take_photo" translatable="false">To begin please take a photo of somebody.</string>
    <string name="take_quiz">Fun Quiz</string>
    <string name="thankyou" translatable="false">Thank you!</string>
    <string name="title_congratulation" translatable="false">Congratulations!</string>
    <string name="title_incorrect" translatable="false">Attention</string>
    <string name="title_notice" translatable="false">Notice</string>
    <string name="title_processing" translatable="false">Processing...</string>
    <string name="title_username" translatable="false">Your name</string>
    <string name="upload_success" translatable="false">Upload Successful</string>
    <string name="viceversa" translatable="false">vice versa.</string>
    <string name="view_videos">View Videos</string>
    <string name="your_answer_">Your Answer: %s</string>
    <string name="your_score_">Your score: %d/%d</string>
    <style name="AppTheme" parent="Theme.AppCompat.Light.DarkActionBar">
        
        <item name="colorPrimary">@color/colorPrimaryDark</item>
        <item name="colorPrimaryDark">@color/colorPrimaryDark</item>
        <item name="colorAccent">@color/colorAccent</item>
    </style>
    <style name="AppTheme.NoActionBar" parent="Theme.AppCompat.Light.NoActionBar">
        
        <item name="colorPrimary">@color/colorPrimaryDark</item>
        <item name="colorPrimaryDark">@color/colorPrimaryDark</item>
        <item name="colorAccent">@color/colorAccent</item>
    </style>
</resources>